A Guide to the Records of the Office of the President, William E. Lavery, 1975-1987
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series V: 1979
  - Condor Design, "Concept: What Will Involvement in Motor Racing do for Virginia Tech?", 1979 (Box 8, Folder 21A)
  - Corp of Cadets, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 22A)
    - Clipping from the "Brazil Herald"
    - Concerns on the Iranian situation and the related problems of Iranian students at Virginia Tech
    - Research summary on the role of gambling in expanding inflation
  - Development, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity and Affirmative Action Committee (2 folders), 1979 (Box 8, Folder 24-25)
  - Fall Administrators' Conference, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Hahn, T. Marshall Jr., 1979 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Homecoming, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Honor System Review Board (2 folders), 1979 (Box 8, Folder 29-30)
  - Information Services, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Institutional Research, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - International Programs, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - International Programs Committee, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - International Student Advisor, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Judicial Committee, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Laboratory Support Services, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Lane Stadium, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Lavery - Personal, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Library Committee, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Mining and Minerals Engineering, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Naming Buildings, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Price's Fork Research Center
    - University Bookstore
    - Biochemistry building
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (3 folders), 1979 (Box 8, Folder 43-44, Box 9, Folder 1)
  - National Brotherhood Citation, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Office of Health and Safety Regulatory Programs, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Personnel - Richmond, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Philippines, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 4A)
  - Pratt Bequest, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Provost, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Public Administration and Policy, Center for, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Research Division, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Retirement, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Reynolds Homestead Research Center, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Sea Grant Program, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Speeches, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - State Council of Higher Education (6 folders), 1979 (Box 9, Folder 14-19)
  - Student Awards and Honors, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Student Engineers' Council, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - University Name, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Vice President for Administration, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs (4 folders), 1979 (Box 9, Folder 24-27)
  - Virginia Department of Agriculture and Commerce, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - VPI [Virginia Polytechnic Institute] Education Foundation, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Tech Student Aid Association, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Tidewater Consortium, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Truck and Ornamental Research Station, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Water Resources Research Center, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Western Region Consortium for Continuing Higher Education, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - William and Mary, College of, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Wine Award, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - YMCA, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Series VI: 1980
  - Commandant of Cadets, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Commencement Exercises, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Fall Faculty Meeting, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 12A)
  - Institutional Research, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Legislators - General Assembly (2 folders), 1980 (Box 10, Folder 14-15)
  - Legislators - US Congress, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Library, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - M - Colleges, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Mississippi State University
    - Fitchburg State College, Massachusetts
  - Mining and Minerals Engineering, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous (2 folders), 1980 (Box 10, Folder 20-21)
    - Notable names in American History
    - Blacksburg Town Council candidates
    - Committee for Intercultural Dialogue
    - National Extension Homemakers Council
    - New River Historical Society
    - Letter from Booker T. Washington
  - Naming Buildings, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Biochemistry building
    - Policy on Commemorative Tributes
    - The Price's Fork facility
  - Pallet and Container Research Center, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Performing Arts and Communications, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Placement, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Public Choice, Center for the Study of, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Reynolds Homestead Research Center (2 folders), 1980 (Box 10, Folder 27-28)
  - ROTC, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Speeches, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Virginia State Advisory Council on Vocational Education
    - The American Legion - Boys State of Virginia
    - Remarks at Cadet Corps Review Honoring General Acuff
    - Extension Conference Luncheon
    - Southeast 4-H Educational Center
  - Virginia Academy of Science, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Virginia Tech Athletic Association, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - William and Mary, College of, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Series VII: 1981
  - Agriculture and Life Sciences, College of (2 folders), 1981 (Box 10, Folder 34-35)
  - Airport and Planes, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Alumni Association - General, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Alumni Distinguished Professor, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - American Council on Education, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Architecture and Urban Studies, College of, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Arts and Sciences, College of, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Attorney General of Virginia, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Bequests, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Blacksburg, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Board of Visitors, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Borderland Coal Co. - Newspaper article, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Budget Division - Connock, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Commencement Exercises, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Committees, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Consortium on Higher Education in Northern Virginia, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Cooperative Education Program, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Corps of Cadets, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Mr. Ray S. Whitt
    - Mr. Miles C. Horton
    - Mrs. Suzanne Heath Manges
    - Mrs. Jane L. Bain
  - Council of Presidents, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Council of Visitors, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Development - General, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Donaldson Brown Center, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Education, College of, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Employee Relations Department, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Energy Task Force, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Engineering and Buildings, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Engineering, College of, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Engineering Science and Mechanics Committee, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Environmental Studies, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity and Affirmative Action Committee, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Equine Medical Center, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Executive Bulletins, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Extension - General (2 folders), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 29-30)
  - Forestry and Wildlife, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Founders Day, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Governor of Virginia, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Office of the Governor - Secretary of Education, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Hotel Roanoke, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - In-State Status Policy, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Internal Audit, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - International Programs, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Invitations - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Residence Management/Residence Hall Federation Leadership Banquet and Reception
    - Christmas Tree Lighting Ceremony
    - Area 9 Special Olympics
    - 'McHappy Day" sponsored by the Juvenile Diabetes Foundation
    - Dedication of the Shot Tower Historical State Park of Wythe County Virginia
  - Kellog Foundation, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Lavery, W.E. - Personal, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Legislators, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Library, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Lynchburg Chapter of Links, Inc., 1981 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Mechanical Engineering Department, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Memos, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 45A)
    - Conflict of Interest Act, 1981
    - Faculty Senate Constitution revision, 1981
    - Organization and staffing changes in central administration, 1981
    - University Policy on Continuing Education, 1981
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Northern Virginia, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Performing Arts and Communications, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Photos, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - "Twelfth- Annual Institute on Coal-Mining Health, Safety and Research"
  - Placement (2 folders), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 50-51)
  - Presidential Inaugural Committee, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Provost, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Reynolds Homestead Research Center, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Roanoke Municipal Airport, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Speeches, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Fall Administrators Conference
    - Cooperative Education - Industries and Universities
    - The University, CRD [Council for Resource Development] and the 1980s
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Student Affairs - Payne, A.C., 1981 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Student Budget Board, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Student Housing, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Student Organizations, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Student Programs and Services, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Student Union, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - University Council and Faculty Senate, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Revision of the Constitution of the University Council
  - University Dean, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - University Distinguished Professors, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - University Services and Auxiliary Enterprises, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - VPI Educational Foundation, Inc., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Tech Student Aid Association, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Water Resources Research Center, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Series VIII: 1982
  - Administrators Conference, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Association - General, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - American Association of University Women (AAUW), 1982 (Box 12, Folder 14A)
  - "Black Life at Virginia Tech", 1982 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Chemistry Department, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Christmas, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education in Northern Virginia, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 18A)
  - Development - Forbes, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Equal Opportunity Employment and Affirmative Action Committee, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Engineering, College of, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Extension - Dean, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Extension - General, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Faculty Receptions, November and December, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Faculty Senate, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Football (2 folders), 1982 (Box 12, Folder 26-27)
  - Forestry and Wildlife, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Founders Day, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Freshman and Transfer Student Reception, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - General Professional Advisory Committee (GPAC), 1982 (Box 12, Folder 30A)
  - George Mason University, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Governor's Day, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Governor of Virginia, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Office of the Governor - Secretary of Education, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Hahn, T. Marshall Jr., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Home Economics, College of, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Honor System, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Information Services, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Institutional Research, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - International Programs, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Lavery, W.E. - Personal, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Legislators - General Assembly, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Library, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Mechanical Engineering Department, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Memos, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 44A)
    - Conflict of Interest Act, 1982
    - Appointment of Dr. Perry as Acting Provost, 1982
    - YMCA Fund Drive, 1982
    - United Fund Campaign, 1982
    - Provost Search, 1982
  - Naming Buildings, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Correspondence with, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Performing Arts and Communications, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Placement, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Planning, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Plant Pathology, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Policy memorandum, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 50A)
    - University-funded merit scholarships program
  - Pratt Request, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - William Preston Society, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Provost, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Public Administration and Policy, Center for, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Public Radio WVWR-FM (3 folders), 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 55 to 12-57)
  - Pulaski Furniture, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Research Division, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - ROTC, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - ROTC Contracts, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Rural Development, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Scholarships and Grants, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Sea Grant, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Security, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Speeches, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Speech Material, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Sporn Award, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Staff Meetings, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - State Educational Assistance Authority, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Student Affairs, Ford S.D., 1982 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Student Housing, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Student Letters - Others, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Student Letters - To and From, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Student Programs and Services - Brown, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Student Union, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - United Way Fund, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - University Dean, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - University Landscaping, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - University Services and Auxiliary Enterprises, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Upward Bound, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Vice President for Administration, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Vice President for Development, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Vice President for Finance, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Virginia Department of Agriculture and Commerce, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce - Luncheons, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - VPI Educational Foundation Inc., 1982 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Water Resources Research Center, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - William H. Ruffner Medal, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Series IX: 1983
  - Agriculture and Life Sciences, College of, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - St. Albans Psychiatric Hospital, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Alumni Distinguished Professor, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Animal Industry Day, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Animal Science Department, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Architecture and Urban Studies, College of, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Blacksburg, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Center for Innovative Technology (3 folders), 1983 (Box 13, Folder 33-35)
  - Commencement, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Corps of Cadets, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Development - University, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Engineering Computing, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Governor of Virginia, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Information Services, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Institutional Research and Planning Analysis - University Fact Book, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - International Programs, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Invitations - Miscellaneous (2 folders), 1983 (Box 13, Folder 44-45)
  - Kellogg Foundation, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Legislators - General Assembly, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Policy memorandum, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 47A)
    - A university core curriculum
  - Research Division, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Reynolds Homestead Research Center, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - ROTC, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Sociology Department, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Speeches, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Student Letters - Others, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Vice-President for Student Affairs, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Academy of Science, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Cooperative Extension Service - Budget Requests, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Department of Agriculture and Commerce, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Water Resources Research Center, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Series X: 1984
  - Aircraft, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1984 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - American Association of University Women (AAUW), 1984 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Biology Department, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Blacksburg, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Budget Division, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Center for Innovative Technology (2 folders), 1984 (Box 14, Folder 15-16)
  - Civil Engineering, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Coal and Energy Research Center, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Commandant of Cadets, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Computer Science Department, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Computing Center, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 21A)
    - Gilbert Linkous Elementary School - Virginia Reading Month, 1984
    - Paul M. Saunders, Saunders Orchard and Nursery, 1984
  - Council of Presidents, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Development - Capital Campaign, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Development - Forbes, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Development - General, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Donaldson Brown Center, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Education, College of, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - English Construction Company Inc., 1984 (Box 14, Folder 27A)
  - Honor System Review Board, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Kellogg Foundation, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Lavery, W. E. - Personal, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Learning Resource Center, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Library, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Memo, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 33A)
    - Conflict of Interest Act, 1984
    - OCR Requirements for Faculty Search and Selection, 1984
    - Campaign for Excellence, 1984
    - The 1984 Legislative Session and Its Impact on the University, 1984
    - Faculty Salary Program, 1983-1984
  - Mill Mountain Zoo, Inc., 1984 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Mining and Minerals Engineering, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Naming Buildings, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Nuclear Reactor Laboratory - College of Engineering, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 36A)
  - Philippines, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Physics Department, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Planning, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Policy memoranda, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 39A)
    - New provisions related to the university core curriculum
    - Course prerequisites
    - Lengthening the drop period
    - University copyright policy
  - Provost, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Public Administration and Policy, Center for, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Retirement, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Reynolds Homestead Research Center, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Richmond Office for Virginia Tech, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 43A)
  - ROTC, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Rural Development, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Scholarships and Grants, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Security, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Senate Grant, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Southern Universities Research Association (SURA), 1984 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Speeches, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Speech Material, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Staff Meeting, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - State Council on Higher Education (3 folders), 1984 (Box 15, Folder 4-6)
  - Student Housing, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Student Programs and Services, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Talent Search Program, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Treasurer and Associate Vice President, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - University Committee for Teaching Excellence, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - University Distinguished Professors, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Upward Bound and National Council of Educational Opportunity Associations (NCEOA), 1984 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Vice President for Administration, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Vice President for Finance, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - VPI Educational Foundation, Inc., 1984 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Truck and Ornamental Research Station, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Water Resources Research Center, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - William Preston Society, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - William H. Ruffner Medal, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Series XI: 1985
  - Accounting - President's Home, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Admissions and Records, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Aerospace and Ocean Engineering, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Affirmative Action Award, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Agronomy Department, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Alumni Association - General, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Alumni Association - President, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Alumni Congratulatory Letters, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - American Association of University Women (AAUW), 1985 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - American Council on Education, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Anaerobe Laboratory, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Animal Industry Day, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Animal Science Department, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Aquatics Program - Petition, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Architecture and Urban Studies, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Attorney General of Virginia, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Contributions to the VPI Educational Fund, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Enrollment Statistics, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity and Affirmative Action Advisory Committee (2 folders), 1985 (Box 15, Folder 43-44)
  - Extension - General, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Forestry and Wildlife, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Founders Day, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Office of the Governor, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Health, Physical Education and Recreation, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - History Department, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Institutional Research, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - International Programs, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Invitations - Miscellaneous (3 folders), 1985 (Box 15, Folder 53-54, Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Jamison, Calvin D., 1985 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Kellogg Foundation, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Lavery, W. E. - Personal (2 folders), 1985 (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
  - Legislators - General Assembly, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Legislators - US Congress, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Library, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda of Understanding, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - State Water Control Board